Hello everyone and welcome to another lesson at EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听另一节EnglishPod课程。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
And I'm Catherine and today we're talking about shopping online.
我是Catherine，今天我们聊聊网上购物。
So this is an elementary level lesson.
这是一节初级水平的课程。
That's right.
没错。
We are going to shop for things online.
我们要在网上买东西。
So before we get started with this dialogue, let's take a look at one word we have for
在开始这段对话之前，我们先来看一个词汇预览中的单词。
you on vocabulary preview.
词汇预览。
Vocabulary preview.
Okay the word we're looking at today is eBay.
好的，我们今天要看的单词是eBay。
eBay.
eBay。
Okay, so this is a proper noun.
好的，这是一个专有名词。
It's an actual website, ebay.com.
它是一个真实的网站，ebay.com。
That's right.
没错。
It's kind of like a store on the internet for people who want to buy used things.
它有点像互联网上的商店，供想买二手物品的人使用。
Okay, so maybe if you have a TV that you don't want anymore, you go on eBay, you put pictures
好的，比如你有一台不想要的电视，你可以上eBay，上传它的照片。
of it online and you offer it and anyone can buy it.
然后发布出来，任何人都可以买。
That's right.
没错。
You can be a buyer, that means you buy things or a seller.
你可以是买家，也就是买东西的人，或者是卖家。
So you sell things.
也就是卖东西的人。
So this is interesting.
这挺有意思的。
Usually you find used things on eBay but you can also find new things.
通常你在eBay上能找到二手货，但也能找到全新的东西。
You can.
没错。
It's kind of like the Chinese website Taobao.
有点像中国的淘宝网站。
I've actually even seen people selling cars on eBay.
我甚至见过有人在eBay上卖车。
Cars?
车？
Yeah.
是啊。
I can't imagine buying a car on the internet.
我无法想象在网上买车。
Really?
真的吗？
No, they have even very luxurious cars on eBay.
不，eBay上甚至还有非常豪华的车。
So we'll talk about more about online shopping a little bit later on.
我们稍后会再聊聊网上购物的事。
But now, why don't we listen to a dialogue for the first time and then we'll come back
但现在，不如我们先听一遍对话，
in just a little bit.
然后过一会儿再回来。
What are you doing?
你在干嘛？
I'm just looking for a nice pillow on eBay.
我正想在eBay上找个好枕头。
You're shopping for a pillow online?
你在网上买枕头？
That's absurd.
真荒唐。
Why?
为什么？
I don't have to leave the house or browse a dozen stores to find what I'm looking for.
我不用出门，也不用逛十几家店就能找到想要的。
This way, I just search for it online quick and easy.
这样，我只要在网上搜一下，又快又方便。
I see.
我明白了。
But how do you pay for it?
但你用什么方式付款呢？
How do you know you aren't going to be ripped off by the seller?
你怎么知道自己不会被卖家骗呢？
Well, the website handles a point system where if the seller does something wrong, people
嗯，这个网站有一套积分系统，如果卖家做错了事，人们
comment negatively and then you know that he or she may not be trustworthy.
会留下负面评论，这样你就知道他或她可能不可信。
Wow, that sounds pretty safe.
哇，听起来挺安全的。
So how do you pay?
那你怎么付款呢？
Do you need a credit card?
需要信用卡吗？
You can use a credit card or your debit card.
你可以用信用卡或借记卡。
They also let you use the PayPal system, which is really safe and fast.
他们也允许你用PayPal系统，这真的很安全又快捷。
I have never had any problems with someone hacking my information or anything.
我从来没遇到过信息被黑客盗取之类的问题。
Do you think I can find a sweater for my dog online?
你觉得我能在网上给我狗买件毛衣吗？
You can find anything.
什么都能找到。
Are you sure you want to start shopping online though?
不过你确定要开始网购吗？
Once you step into this world, there is no turning back.
一旦踏入这个领域，可就回不了头了。
Let's do it.
那就开始吧。
Alright, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So now we have four key words for you on Language Takeaway.
现在在“语言小贴士”环节，我们为你准备了四个关键词。
Language Takeaway.
语言小贴士。
The first word you might have already heard us use already.
第一个词你可能已经听我们用过了。
We're talking about going on the internet to do something.
我们正在讨论上网做某事。
So we say to go online.
所以我们说“上线”。
Okay.
好的。
So by saying that you are going online, you say that you are using the internet.
所以当你说“上线”时，意思是你正在使用互联网。
That's right.
没错。
So you can shop for something online.
所以你可以在网上购物。
Online means the internet, right?
“在线”就是指互联网，对吧？
On the internet.
在互联网上。
So we don't say in the internet.
所以我们不说“在互联网里”。
We say we're on the internet.
我们说“在互联网上”。
For example, he's been on the internet all day long.
例如，他整天都在上网。
I want to use the computer.
我想用电脑。
Okay, so I can say he's been online all day long.
好的，所以我可以说他整天都在线上。
That's right.
没错。
Okay.
好的。
So that is online.
所以那就是“在线”。
And when we go online and we are looking through different websites or maybe we are looking
当我们上网时，浏览不同的网站，或者可能在看
at items on eBay, we are browsing.
eBay上的商品，我们就是在“浏览”。
Okay, the verb here is to browse.
好的，这里的动词是“浏览”。
Now to browse is to look at, but not carefully.
“浏览”就是看看，但不仔细看。
Just to look at with maybe the idea to shop or to buy later.
只是看看，也许有想法以后购物或购买。
Okay.
好的。
So you can use browse for online things, but you can also use it for physical things like
所以你可以用“浏览”来形容网上看东西，但也可以用于实体物品，比如
you are in a shop, you are browsing.
你在商店里，你在浏览。
That's right.
没错。
So I can go to a clothing store and I can browse.
所以我可以去服装店浏览。
For example, if the woman at the clothing store says, would you like to buy something?
比如，如果服装店的女店员问你想买点什么，
I say, no, I'm just browsing.
我说，不，我只是随便看看。
I'm just looking.
我只是看看。
Okay.
好的。
Very good.
很好。
And then when they were talking about eBay and how it works, the person mentioned that
然后当他们谈论eBay以及它是如何运作时，那个人提到
they have a point system.
他们有一个积分系统。
All right.
好的。
A point system.
一个积分系统。
Now, this is something you hear about a lot on websites these days.
现在，这是你在当今网站上经常听到的东西。
For example, many websites have different users.
例如，许多网站有不同的用户。
And so how do I know which users or which in this case, sellers are the best?
那么我怎么知道哪些用户，或者在这种情况下，哪些卖家是最好的呢？
Well, we have a point system.
嗯，我们有一个积分系统。
More points means better, fewer points means worse.
积分越多越好，积分越少越差。
You might also call this a star system.
你也可以称之为星级系统。
So basically a point system is a way to show who is a very good community member and who
所以基本上，积分系统是一种显示谁是优秀社区成员、谁不是的方式。
is not.
谁不是。
That's right.
没错。
And that takes us to our next word.
这就引出了我们的下一个词。
So if a person has a lot of points in their point system, that means they are trustworthy.
所以如果一个人在积分系统中有很多积分，那就意味着他们是值得信赖的。
Okay.
好的。
Trustworthy is an adjective.
“值得信赖”是一个形容词。
He is trustworthy.
他是值得信赖的。
They are trustworthy.
他们是值得信赖的。
This means that I can trust them.
这意味着我可以信任他们。
They are reliable.
他们是可靠的。
That's right.
没错。
So I don't think they will lie to me.
所以我认为他们不会对我撒谎。
I don't think they will cheat me.
我认为他们不会欺骗我。
Okay.
好的。
So a person can be trustworthy.
所以一个人可以是值得信赖的。
A company can be trustworthy.
一家公司可以是值得信赖的。
Right.
对。
Or you could say, he never pays me back.
或者你可以说，他从不还我钱。
He's not very trustworthy when I lend him money.
我借钱给他时，他不太值得信赖。
Okay.
好的。
Very good.
很好。
So four key words there.
所以这里有四个关键词。
Why don't we listen to them again in our dialogue?
我们为什么不在对话中再听一遍呢？
And we'll be back shortly.
我们马上回来。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I'm just looking for a nice pillow on eBay.
我只是在eBay上找一个好枕头。
You're shopping for a pillow online?
你在网上买枕头？
That's absurd.
这太荒谬了。
Why?
为什么？
I don't have to leave the house or browse a dozen stores to find what I'm looking for.
我不必出门或逛十几家店就能找到我要的东西。
This way, I just search for it online quick and easy.
这样，我只需在网上搜索，又快又方便。
I see.
我明白了。
But how do you pay for it?
但你怎么付款呢？
How do you know you aren't going to be ripped off by the seller?
你怎么知道你不会被卖家骗？
Well, the website handles a point system where if the seller does something wrong, people
嗯，网站有一个积分系统，如果卖家做错了什么，人们
comment negatively.
会给出负面评论。
And then you know that he or she may not be trustworthy.
然后你就知道他或她可能不值得信赖。
Wow, that sounds pretty safe.
哇，听起来挺安全的。
So how do you pay?
那你怎么付款呢？
Do you need a credit card?
你需要信用卡吗？
You can use a credit card or your debit card.
你可以用信用卡或借记卡。
They also let you use the PayPal system, which is really safe and fast.
他们也允许你使用PayPal系统，这非常安全快捷。
I have never had any problems with someone hacking my information or anything.
我从来没有遇到过有人黑我信息之类的问题。
Do you think I can find a sweater for my dog online?
你觉得我能在网上给我狗找件毛衣吗？
You can find anything.
你什么都能找到。
Are you sure you want to start shopping online though?
不过你确定要开始网上购物吗？
Once you step into this world, there is no turning back.
一旦你踏入这个世界，就没有回头路了。
Let's do it.
我们开始吧。
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So now we have three key phrases that we saw in our dialogue.
所以现在我们有三个关键短语，我们在对话中看到了。
And let's take a look at those now in Fluency Builder.
让我们现在在流利度构建器中看看它们。
Fluency Builder.
流利度构建器。
Well, the first phrase we have here is related to that last word we had, trustworthy.
嗯，我们这里的第一个短语与我们上一个词“值得信赖”有关。
Someone is not trustworthy if they will rip you off.
如果一个人会骗你，那他就不可信赖。
Okay.
好的。
Okay, so it's a phrasal verb, to rip you off or to rip off.
好的，所以这是一个短语动词，“骗你”或“欺骗”。
To rip someone off.
欺骗某人。
That's right.
没错。
So, they ripped him off.
所以，他们宰了他一笔。
He ripped her off.
他宰了她一笔。
This means to steal money from someone or to cheat someone.
这意思是偷别人的钱或欺骗别人。
Right.
对。
So, let's say if a pair of shoes usually in a store costs $50 and then your friend sells
比如说，如果一双鞋在商店里通常卖50美元，然后你的朋友卖
them to you for $200, your friend ripped you off.
给你200美元，你的朋友就宰了你一笔。
That's right.
没错。
He ripped you off.
他宰了你一笔。
That's not a good friend.
那可不是什么好朋友。
He's not very trustworthy.
他不太可信。
All right.
好吧。
So now when they were talking about how safe it is to make purchases online, the person
所以当他们讨论网上购物有多安全时，那个人
explained that it's pretty safe and that no one has ever hacked his information.
解释说这挺安全的，而且从来没人黑过他的信息。
Okay.
好的。
So, this is an important verb that has to do with the internet.
所以，这是一个与互联网相关的重要动词。
To hack information is to steal information on the internet.
黑信息就是在互联网上偷信息。
So, someone who hacks, who steals this information is called a hacker.
所以，那些黑别人、偷信息的人被称为黑客。
Okay.
好的。
And this is something that's very bad.
这是件非常糟糕的事。
We want to go to secure and safe websites because we don't want people to hack our personal
我们想上安全可靠的网站，因为我们不想让别人黑我们的个人
information.
信息。
That's right.
没错。
Okay, so the verb is to hack.
好的，所以这个动词就是“黑”。
And finally, in the end when they were going to look for a sweater for a dog, the person
最后，在结尾他们要给狗找一件毛衣时，那个人
said, you know what?
说，你知道吗？
This is great.
这太棒了。
Are you sure you want to start to shop online?
你确定要开始网上购物吗？
Once you do this, there is no turning back.
一旦你这么做，就没有回头路了。
Oh, I love this phrase.
哦，我喜欢这个短语。
There's no turning back.
没有回头路了。
So this is, well, you think about someone who's leaving.
这就像，嗯，你想到一个要离开的人。
You say there's no turning back.
你说没有回头路了。
You can't go back.
你回不去了。
You can't return to where you were.
你无法回到原来的状态。
This is something we say as a warning.
这是我们作为警告说的话。
So listen, this is your final decision.
所以听着，这是你的最终决定。
If you say yes, you cannot change your mind.
如果你说“是”，你就不能改变主意。
You cannot say no later.
你以后不能说“不”。
So you can't turn back later.
所以你以后不能回头。
That's right.
没错。
So there's no turning back now.
所以现在没有回头路了。
Okay, no turning back.
好的，没有回头路。
Very good.
非常好。
Interesting phrases, keywords and everything.
有趣的短语、关键词和所有内容。
So we should listen to this dialogue one last time and we'll be back to talk with you a
所以我们应该再听一遍这段对话，然后我们会回来再跟你们聊
little bit more.
一会儿。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I'm just looking for a nice pillow on eBay.
我只是在eBay上找一个好枕头。
You're shopping for a pillow online?
你在网上买枕头？
That's absurd.
这太荒谬了。
Why?
为什么？
I don't have to leave the house or browse a dozen stores to find what I'm looking for.
我不需要出门或逛十几家店就能找到我要的东西。
This way, I just search for it online quick and easy.
这样，我只需在网上搜一下，又快又方便。
I see.
我明白了。
But how do you pay for it?
但你怎么付款呢？
How do you know you aren't going to be ripped off by the seller?
你怎么知道你不会被卖家宰一笔？
Well, the website handles a point system where if the seller does something wrong, people
嗯，网站有一个评分系统，如果卖家做错了什么，人们
comment negatively.
会给出负面评论。
And then you know that he or she may not be trustworthy.
然后你就知道他或她可能不可信。
Wow, that sounds pretty safe.
哇，听起来挺安全的。
So how do you pay?
那你怎么付款？
Do you need a credit card?
你需要信用卡吗？
You can use a credit card or your debit card.
你可以用信用卡或借记卡。
They also let you use the PayPal system, which is really safe and fast.
他们也允许你用PayPal系统，这真的很安全又快速。
I have never had any problems with someone hacking my information or anything.
我从来没遇到过有人黑我信息之类的问题。
Do you think I can find a sweater for my dog online?
你觉得我能在网上给我的狗找到一件毛衣吗？
You can find anything.
你什么都能找到。
Are you sure you want to start shopping online though?
不过你确定要开始网上购物吗？
Once you step into this world, there is no turning back.
一旦你踏入这个世界，就没有回头路了。
Let's do it.
来吧。
Alright so now talking about online shopping, have you ever bought anything online?
好的，现在聊聊网上购物，你曾经在网上买过东西吗？
Use your credit card online.
在网上用你的信用卡。
I have.
我买过。
I've used my credit card on Amazon.com to purchase books on the internet.
我在Amazon.com上用信用卡在网上买过书。
But I know that you are much more of a fan of online shopping.
但我知道你更喜欢网上购物。
You use the Chinese website Taobao all the time.
你一直用中国网站淘宝。
Yeah.
是啊。
Well actually, I wrote this dialogue and it's kind of based on something real because you
嗯，其实我写了这段对话，它有点基于真实情况，因为你
know sometimes going to the stores, it can be great and you can see things and physically
知道有时候去商店，可以很好，你能看到东西并亲手
touch them.
摸到它们。
But I'm a little bit more practical.
但我更实际一点。
I know exactly what I want or maybe I saw it.
我清楚知道自己想要什么，或者可能已经看中了。
So I don't want to have to go to the stores and deal with haggling or negotiating or sometimes
所以我不想跑去商店，还要讨价还价，有时候
it's even more expensive.
甚至更贵。
So I just, from the comfort of my own home, just put in my debit card number and buy things
所以我就在自己舒适的家里，输入借记卡号，买东西
online and I get it delivered overnight.
网购，然后隔天就能送到。
Well, and you never go shopping now.
嗯，那你现在都不去购物了。
Well, shopping you have to go to the clothing store for clothes, the video game store for
购物的话，你得去服装店买衣服，去游戏店买
video games and on the internet, it's all in one place.
游戏，而在网上，所有东西都在一个地方。
You're at home, you're in your pajamas, you use your credit card.
你在家，穿着睡衣，用信用卡就行。
And the cool thing is that you can even, sometimes you want to buy small things.
而且酷的是，你甚至有时候想买小东西。
Like in this case, maybe a pillow or you want to buy, like recently I bought some candles,
比如这次，可能是个枕头，或者像最近我买了些蜡烛，
some decorative candles.
一些装饰蜡烛。
So I don't know, do you really want to go out downtown, look for the candle shop where
所以我不知道，你真的想跑到市中心，找那家卖蜡烛的店
you can get them?
去买吗？
You can just do it online.
你直接在网上搞定就行了。
Do it online.
网上搞定。
Let us know, do you shop on the internet?
告诉我们，你在网上购物吗？
If you do, what kind of services do you use?
如果购物，你用什么服务？
What stores do you go to?
你去哪些商店？
Let us know.
告诉我们。
Our website is EnglishPod.com.
我们的网站是 EnglishPod.com。
We hope to see you there.
希望在那里见到你。
All right.
好了。
Bye everyone.
大家再见。
realidadv.com